Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mercyogbenjuwa-178805227 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Secure Coding
SOAP
Microsoft SQL Server

Languages

French (Elementary)
Idoma (Full Professional)
English (Full Professional)
Pidgin English (Full Professional)
Hausa (Limited Working)

Certifications

Product Management

Blockchain Technology/
Cryptocurrency
Scrum Fundamentals Certified (SFC)
Secure Coding

Mercy Ogbenjuwa

Software Engineer || Innovation Specialist || Tech Enthusiast Lagos, Lagos State, Nigeria

Summary

Hi, I'm Mercy Onyoibo Ogbenjuwa, a computer enthusiast who loves solving problems with code. I learned a lot about computers at the University of Bingham. I've worked in finance, health, education, and tech industry.

I enjoy figuring out tricky code puzzles and working well with different teams. I'm always learning about the newest tech stuff.

If you have cool tech projects or ideas, let's chat! Connect with me on LinkedIn, and we can use technology to make awesome things happen together. Excited to start this tech journey with you!

Experience

Optimus Bank Software Engineer (Backend .NET) April 2023 - Present (10 months) Lagos State, Nigeria

Talosmart
Software Engineer (Node.js Backend)
September 2021 - March 2023 (1 year 7 months)
Lagos, Lagos State, Nigeria

Heirs Insurance Technical Support January 2021 - August 2021 (8 months) Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

Education

Bingham University

Bachelor of science, Computer and Information Sciences